Learn to drive
Spider-Man
I got a Parker Peter
I’m Parker
P-P-Peter Parker
Peter Parker
Test time
baby
Sweet ride
for a 15 year old
kid
Yeah It's actually
my friend
Tony’s
It's a prototype
I wish I had
a friend
named Tony
*slaps sticker on*
Put your hands
in 9 and 3
*confused*
*places them correctly*
I thought it was
10 and 2
It was 10
and 2
But now it's 9
and 3
You’re gonna lose
5 points
for that
*sudden stop*
*automatic audi braking*
*escalade in front*
*screams*
*stops it in time*
woho
Whoa!
*looks at Peter*
Carry on
*cruising along*
*passing cars*
Alright
Watch this
*AI audi button*
Put that button
*autopilot activates*
No hands
Hey hey
hey Hey
hey
Sorry
sorry
Don't do that
won’t
Not again
*motions to him*
Let’s pass someone
*gets ready*
Okay
Let’s go
*speeding ahead*
slow down
whoa!
ohhh!
*angrily points at him*
don’t be a hero!
superhero*
The grand finale
Parallel parking
*presses a button*
*hands off wheel*
*wheel turning*
*instructor ain’t happy*
And we
parked
I guess turning
the wheel
too much for you
kids
nowadays huh?
Let’s go
*bank robbery*
*unbuckles seatbelt*
*Spider-Man swings by*
you fail
I fail
Bad guys?!
So did i pass?
*looks at him*
*gets scared*
woahhh!!